ticketgenie.in 2019-01-26

# Ticketgenie | PrivacyPolicy

######  The type of information we gather from you

This Privacy Policy explains how we record and use information about you and the choices you can make about how the information is collected and used. 

What we do with Personally Identifiable information 

We collect information through technology to make our website more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to one of our websites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our websites. We may combine this information with personally. 

######  Use of Cookies

Our websites also use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing the website. We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, when you return to one of our websites after logging in, cookies provide information to the website so that the website will remember who you are. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services will not function properly. If you turn off the cookies, some of our services will not function properly and you will not have access to many of the features that make your web experience smoother. 

######  We will only pass on your information to third parties in the following situations

1\. If this was clearly stated at the time of collection or registration and, where required, if you have given permission for this.   
2\. If we employ another organization to perform tasks on our behalf - such as hosting the Site. In this case, the organizations may only use your information to fulfill this specific task.   
3\. If we sell our business to another organization or merge with other businesses. In this case, the buyer will only be able to use your information as set out in this Privacy Policy.   
4\. If we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary for legal proceedings. We may also disclose member information when we believe at good faith that applicable law or regulation requires it.   
5\. If we use third party processors to administer and process for the purposes notified in the Privacy Policy. We may also share details with third parties (such as auditors or legal advisors) to obtain advice. Any such processing will be governed by an agreement in the form required by law, preserving any statutory data protection rights. 

######  Transaction Security

Our top priority in processing orders through our website is your security. We secure credit card processing services to ensure that your personal information remains yours and yours alone. We will handle your private information in a secure and professional manner - we hold ourselves accountable to our members in good standing with the Better Business Bureau Online, a supervising organization overseeing the practices of its affiliates in order to protect consumers.   
Our website uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purpose, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on our websites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our websites. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send our guests to determine whether our guests have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable. 

######  Links to other websites

You should be aware that when you are on our websites you could be directed to other websites where the personal information collected is outside the control of our website. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement the click may take you off the Site. The privacy policy of the new website will govern the information obtained from you on such website. 

######  Changes to this policy

We may change this policy and our terms and conditions from time to time and will post the latest version of the privacy policy on the Site. If we ever wish to use your personal information in a way which is incompatible with the information in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so with your consent.
